topsfund.org 2011-12-24

# :.:.:TopsFund.Com:.:.:

Your Privacy is Our Priority 

Privacy Policy At TopsFund, we are concerned with safeguarding your personal information. You have entrusted us with an important role in your financial future. We are committed to keeping your personal information secure. We are committed to the principles stated in this notice for all our customers. This applies to past, present and future owners of our products. 

When you visit our site, we may collect information about your use of our site through "cookies". Cookies are small bits of information transferred to your computer's hard drive that allow us to know how often a user visits our site and the activities they are most interested in performing. We require the acceptance of cookies to enable users to take full advantage of specific services offered. We may also require you to accept cookies placed by a third party supporting this activity on our behalf. 

The cookies collect certain technical and navigational information only, such as computer browser type, internet protocol address, pages visited, and average time spent on our websites. In addition, we capture the paths taken as you move from page to page (i.e. your "click stream" activity). This information allows us to enhance your experience while on our site. 

Finally, we use "cookies" to establish and maintain a logged-in connection while you are in the secure section(s) of our website. For example, when you visit your account, perform transactions, update contact information or perform other activity the "cookie" allows you to navigate from page to page in a secure fashion without having to repeatedly log-in. 

We may monitor or record any telephone call we have with you. The content of the call may also be retained. We may inform you prior to proceeding with the call of this possibility. This is to establish a record of the information you provide, to ensure that your instructions are followed properly and to ensure customer service levels are maintained. 

When you use a link to go from TopsFund to another web site, the TopsFund Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other web site is subject to the rules and policies of that site. We encourage you to read the rules and policies of the sites you visit to further understand their procedures for collecting, using, and disclosing personal information. 

TopsFund strictly protects the personal information you provide against unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, destruction, loss or misuse. Your personal information is protected by physical, electronic and procedural safeguards in accordance with federal and state standards. These safeguards include appropriate procedures for access and use of electronic data, provisions for the secure transmission of sensitive personal information on our website, and telephone system authentication procedures. Additionally, we limit access to your personal information to those TopsFund employees who need your personal information in order to provide products or services to you. 

TopsFund will protect your information with appropriate safeguards and security measures. We have thorough security standards and procedures to protect all information and all TopsFund personnel have signed a confidentiality agreement which governs their treatment of all personal information. 

Please check this privacy policy periodically for changes. Although we reserve the right to modify or supplement this privacy policy, we will provide notice to you on this website of any major changes.
